Sharad has joined us with which news? Sharad,
good morning for good morning. Pooja, so
ICC Lombard will first be in Fox
where Idea has given approval
that SBI Mutual Fund can take up to 10%
stake in the company. Inox
and Inox Wind Energy will be in Fox. Now
Inox Wind Energy which is going to be
in my Inox Wind and now the shareholder
ratio has come, if you hold 10 shares in
Inox Wind Energy, you will
get almost 158% of your shares in Inox Wind.
After this, the important thing is that
this is going to be beneficial for the share holders of Inox Wind Energy.
Balrampur Chini Mill, in this, Suicide General has bought
almost 5%. Takli Maa Infra has also bought
39 lakh shares, the buying of this has been
seen from Fahrenheit. There has been a bang in Usha Martin
in Motilal Oswal Mutual Fund
and the deal is actually very
important because the non-promoters
capital has completely exited.  10% of the stock has been
sold and their investment has generated returns of around 15 times.
If in November 2014,
mutual funds like Kuwait Investment Authority
and another big name Suicide General, almost 10
%, have placed orders. Talking about orders,
Engineer India has received an order
from ONGC and an order of around 500
crores. HCL has also received an order of around 81
crores.
Talking about SGVN, an order has come for 100 MW
whose project cost is around 1400
crores. JSW Steel
is the preferred bidder, you mean leaves, and this is the
iron and is in the Goa segment.
Apart from this, promoter action was seen in Aarti Drugs.
Around 0.3% of one percent take has been
sold. The promoted time is green.
And finally, I will talk about Red Gen, where
this Capital has also increased its stake from
2% to 5.2%. Congratulations, and this
acquisition took place on 1st June.